{
    "subject": "resource/Geoff_Love",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Film_score",
    "human_readable": "Geoff Love's genre is Film score.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6388503909111023,
            "question": "What kind of musical scores does Geoff Love create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064903140068054,
            "question": "What genre of music is Geoff Love known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5064074993133545,
            "question": "Can you name a genre associated with Geoff Love's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4301040768623352,
            "question": "Geoff Love's work is primarily used in what type of productions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4207145571708679,
            "question": "Which musical style characterizes Geoff Love's compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36681869626045227,
            "question": "What is the dominant theme in Geoff Love's compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32412609457969666,
            "question": "Geoff Love is a composer specializing in what type of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3071812689304352,
            "question": "What kind of music does Geoff Love compose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27340564131736755,
            "question": "What is the main focus of Geoff Love's musical output?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2697645127773285,
            "question": "Geoff Love's music often accompanies what type of media?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Geoff Love's genre is Film score.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5844_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main focus of Geoff Love's musical output?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5844_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Geoff Love compose?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5844_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Geoff Love is a composer specializing in what type of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5844_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5844_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Geoffrey (Geoff) Love, confirming that he was an arranger and composer of film themes, which aligns with the statement that his genre is film score."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}